<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content"><channel><title>BLM Funds</title><description>Donate to support BLM.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 5 Jun 2020 18:11:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Fri, 5 Jun 2020 18:11:44 -0700</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://blm-donate.com/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/alliance-of-californians-for-community-empowerment</guid><title>Alliance of Californians for Community Empowerment (ACCE) Action</title><description>The Alliance of Californians for Community Empowerment (ACCE) Action is a grassroots, member-led, statewide community organization working with more than 15,000 members across California.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/alliance-of-californians-for-community-empowerment</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.acceaction.org/">Alliance of Californians for Community Empowerment (ACCE) Action</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.acceaction.org/donate">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Alliance of Californians for Community Empowerment (ACCE) Action is a grassroots, member-led, statewide community organization working with more than 15,000 members across California. ACCE is dedicated to raising the voices of everyday Californians, neighborhood by neighborhood, to fight for the policies and programs we need to improve our communities and create a brighter future.</p><p>Change from the bottom up: We take seriously our commitment to ground-up organizing to build a strong people’s movement that can create transformative community change. Our local neighborhood chapters and issue committees, led by ACCE Action member leaders, meet regularly to strategize and plan campaigns. Central to this work is the belief that there’s power in numbers and in collective action – ACCE Action members and their allies frequently “take to the streets” with rallies, town halls, and other actions to make their voices heard.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/atlanta-black-owned-business-relief</guid><title>Atlanta Black Owned Business Relief</title><description>Currently raising funds to support the following business an initiatives in Atlanta and other various cities.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/atlanta-black-owned-business-relief</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/atlanta-black-owned-business-relief">Atlanta Black Owned Business Relief</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/atlanta-black-owned-business-relief">Donate Here</a></h2><p>This fundraiser is for Atlanta Owned Black Business Owners affected by the protests, riots, and looting. You must be a verified Atlanta Black Business owner to receive support. Please donate whatever you can donate! Funds will be used to support and repair any damages that have been done during these protests, riots and looting acts. We begin supporting and rebuilding our community by having one another during these times. Our goal is to support Atlanta, however other cities are in consideration so if you know any businesses in other cities please let us know and donate!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/atlanta-solidarity-fund</guid><title>Atlanta Solidarity Fund</title><description>The Atlanta Solidarity Fund is a fund to support people in Atlanta who have been arrested for taking action against social injustice.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/atlanta-solidarity-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://actionnetwork.org/groups/atlanta-solidarity-fund">Atlanta Solidarity Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://actionnetwork.org/fundraising/support-justiceforgeorgefloyd-protesters-in-atlanta">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Atlanta Solidarity Fund is a fund to support people in Atlanta who have been arrested for taking action against social injustice.</p><p>Focused primarily on bailing out arrestees, with priority for those who have the most need.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/austin-justice-coalition</guid><title>The Austin Justice Coalition</title><description>The Austin Justice Coalition (AJC) serves people who are historically and systematically impacted by gentrification, segregation, over policing, a lack of educational and employment opportunities, and other institutional forms of racism in Austin.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/austin-justice-coalition</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://austinjustice.org/">The Austin Justice Coalition</a></h1><h2><a href="https://austinjustice.org/donations/donate/">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Austin Justice Coalition (AJC) serves people who are historically and systematically impacted by gentrification, segregation, over policing, a lack of educational and employment opportunities, and other institutional forms of racism in Austin.</p><p>AJC’s mission is to improve the quality of life for people of color by helping them be the driving force behind their own liberation.</p><p>AJC strives to narrow the scope of the criminal justice system and to usher in transformative justice that no longer relies on criminalization and punitive excess, but instead has human dignity as its core organizing principle and defers to community-based initiatives to improve public safety</p><p>AJC fosters racial reckoning and reconciliation in Austin by acknowledging the ties to racism across systems that are leading to the decreasing Black and Brown populations, and centering all of its programs, initiatives, and policies across quality of life areas on racial equity and building community power.</p><p>AJC responds to opportunities to make changes that are in keeping with AJC priorities and the interests of its community, as they arise.</p><p>As AJC’s founder likes to say, “Our success in the past has been running through the door that is cracked and breaking it open.”</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/bay-area-anti-repression-committee</guid><title>Bay Area Anti-Repression Committee (ARC)</title><description>Originally formed to support Occupy Oakland actions, the Bay Area Anti-Repression Committee (ARC) stands against political repression and is in solidarity with all those who challenge the state, capitalism and other forms of systemic oppression and domination.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/bay-area-anti-repression-committee</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://antirepressionbayarea.com/">Bay Area Anti-Repression Committee (ARC)</a></h1><h2><a href="https://rally.org/ARCbailfund">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Originally formed to support Occupy Oakland actions, the Bay Area Anti-Repression Committee (ARC) stands against political repression and is in solidarity with all those who challenge the state, capitalism and other forms of systemic oppression and domination. We provide support for actions that are anti-patriarchal, anti-racist, anti-imperialist &amp; anti-capitalist. Our support work comes primarily in the form of education, information and referrals. We also manage an anti-repression bail fund for those that do not have the resources to bail or bond themselves. We are a first resort for education and information on solidarity and a last resort for financial support.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-cleveland</guid><title>Black Lives Matter Cleveland</title><description>Local Cleveland Base of Black Lives Matter</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-cleveland</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.facebook.com/BLM216/">Black Lives Matter Cleveland</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.paypal.me/blmcle">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Local Cleveland Base of Black Lives Matter</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-houston</guid><title>BLM Houston</title><description>Black Lives Matter Houston is an organization that addresses the issues that affects Black folks and collaborates with partners to build a healthy, educated and financially stable Black community.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-houston</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.blmhouston.com/">BLM Houston</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.paypal.me/blmhou">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Black Lives Matter Houston is an organization that addresses the issues that affects Black folks and collaborates with partners to build a healthy, educated and financially stable Black community. Our ultimate goal is to pave a path for Black power and liberation where it is understood that ALL BLACK LIVES MATTER. Our Mission is to build a movement that transforms Houston into a city that allows Black Houston to grow and thrive.</p><p>***Black Lives Matter Houston came into existence during the aftermath of the murder of Mike Brown and was started on the ground in Ferguson/St. Louis, MO as Black Lives Matter Texas. As individual chapters sprung up, our focus shifted to the city of Houston, our home base.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-la</guid><title>Black Lives Matter - Los Angeles</title><description>Black Lives Matter - Los Angeles is the first chapter to form in what is now the global network.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-la</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.blmla.org/">Black Lives Matter - Los Angeles</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/blmla">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Black Lives Matter - Los Angeles is the first chapter to form in what is now the global network. Organizers who are among the original members of Black Lives Matter poured into the streets on July 13, 2013, the day that George Zimmerman was acquitted in the murder of Trayvon Martin. Thousands of folks initially gathered in Leimert Park and the Crenshaw District, then engaged in intuitive organizing, shutting down spaces that represented White supremacy, like the Expo train line, the 10 freeway, Hollywood &amp; Highland, and USC. Three days into the organic eruption, folks were called together by Patrisse Cullors, who had been in conversation with Alicia Garza and Opal Tometi about how to build a “movement not a moment.” On July 15, 2013, roughly 30 organizers gathered in the courtyard of St. Elmo’s Village, a historic Black artist community, and committed our lives to the Black freedom struggle, adopting a womanist/Black nationalist framework, with a queer and trans lens.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-louisville</guid><title>Stand Up Sundays - Black Lives Matter Louisville</title><description>Stand Up Sundays is a community building coalition &amp; space to combat factors in opposition to BlackLivesMatter.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-louisville</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://blackliveslouisville.org/">Stand Up Sundays - Black Lives Matter Louisville</a></h1><h2><a href="https://blackliveslouisville.org/stand-up-sundays/donate/">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Stand Up Sundays is a community building coalition &amp; space to combat factors in opposition to #BlackLivesMatter. However, we, as well as the entire social justice community in Louisville, KY, work everyday through our programming to combat violence by educating, informing and training our community about the systemic issues that plague us.</p><p>We make sure that we address and agitate those at the policy level (making the city accountable and calling on transparency from local/state government), showing up and showing out (protesting, or providing programming that fuels our community with the tools they need to make peace with their neighbors; grassroots initiatives of to build the change we want to see. We invite those within the community to join us in building a larger coalition to achieve these goals. We invite those from the social justice community to join us as we condemn the attack of black bodies, minds, and spirit. We call on you to assist in the liberation of all people by the liberation of black lives.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-seattle</guid><title>Black Lives Matter Seattle-King County</title><description>Black Lives Matter Seattle-King County is a 501(c)(4) nonprofit organization which primarily focuses on advocacy and direct action.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/blm-seattle</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://blacklivesseattle.org/">Black Lives Matter Seattle-King County</a></h1><h2><a href="https://blacklivesseattle.org/donate/">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Black Lives Matter Seattle-King County is a 501(c)(4) nonprofit organization which primarily focuses on advocacy and direct action.</p><p>The core activists and organizers of BLM Seattle King County is a group of Black and other people of color focused on dismantling anti-black systems and policies of oppression. The strategy team meetings regularly around Seattle to direct these efforts. Events, meetings, communications and admin needs are volunteer led. Moderators for the Facebook page are on the About/Page Info tab. To contact us or attend the next strategy team meeting email us at info@blacklivesseattle.org</p><p>*BLM Seattle-King County is not affiliated with the Black Liberation Movement or the #BlackLivesMatter Seattle Action Group.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/bole-ethiopian-cuisine</guid><title>Bole Ethiopian Cuisine</title><description>From the start, Bolé was a community driven business, this misfortune has taught all of us that community is what we all have when everything else is stripped away. Therefore, upon the overwhelming request by many of you, we have set up this platform so that you can donate for the initiation of the ‘Re-building Bolé’ project as you see fit.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/bole-ethiopian-cuisine</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/rebuilding-bole-ethiopian-cuisine?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Bole Ethiopian Cuisine</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/rebuilding-bole-ethiopian-cuisine?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Donate Here</a></h2><p>George Floyd's life mattered! Our community is hurt and we are hurting with them.<br><br>As we silently watched our beloved Bolé went up in flames, it was heartbreaking to witness, what we all considered our home, reduced to ashes. What is positive? It is witnessing the overwhelming messages and well wishes that Solomon, Rekik, and the Bolé staff have received. And we thank you, on behalf of the entire family for standing with us when everything else seems like it has fallen beneath our feet. It is comforting to know that we are not alone in thinking that Bolé was not just a restaurant for us, Bolé was the pillar of the community. Bolé was our home away from home. Because your feedback to this unspeakable misfortune is to rise up, to rebuild, and to become the Bolé you all are accustomed to. And with your unyielding support, we are confident will have you dining at your clean tables in no time.</p><p>As you might have also known, the irreplaceable damage was not only caused to Bolé restaurant. Bolé Express, the fast food version of the Bolé franchise, due to open on Sunday, May 31st, 2020 was also burned to the ground. Solomon and the entire crew spent the last 8 months building Bolé Express and they are incredibly proud of the vision to offer an alternative to our busy customers by grabbing their meals with a 2-minute turn around service.</p><p>From the start, Bolé was a community driven business, this misfortune has taught all of us that community is what we all have when everything else is stripped away. Therefore, upon the overwhelming request by many of you, we have set up this platform so that you can donate for the initiation of the ‘Re-building Bolé’ project as you see fit.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/brooklyn-bommunity-bail-fund</guid><title>Brooklyn Community Bail Fund</title><description>Brooklyn Community Bail Fund is committed to challenging the racism, inequality, and injustice of a criminal legal system and immigration and deportation regime that disproportionately target and harm low-income communities of color.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/brooklyn-bommunity-bail-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://brooklynbailfund.org/">Brooklyn Community Bail Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://brooklynbailfund.org/donate">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Brooklyn Community Bail Fund is committed to challenging the racism, inequality, and injustice of a criminal legal system and immigration and deportation regime that disproportionately target and harm low-income communities of color.</p><p>As a New York State-chartered charitable bail fund since 2015, BCBF has paid bail for nearly 5,000 presumptively innocent New Yorkers, effectively securing over 750 years of freedom for clients who would otherwise have been sent to Rikers while awaiting trial because they could not afford even small amounts of bail.</p><p>Since 2018, BCBF's New York Immigration Freedom Fund program has paid over $3 million in immigration bond to secure the freedom of more than 400 immigrant New Yorkers from ICE detention and reunite them with their families and communities.</p><p>But we know that paying bail alone cannot solve the problem. That’s why BCBF is committed to challenging wealth-based detention in all forms and proud to serve as an incubator of high impact initiatives, often in partnership with other community-based organizations, that target legislative policy reform and systems change.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/charleston-protestor-fund</guid><title>Charleston, SC Protestor Fund</title><description>This is a general community fund to help any Black Lives Matter protestors in the Charleston, SC area receive bail funds should they need it.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/charleston-protestor-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/charleston-sc-protestor-fund">Charleston, SC Protestor Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/charleston-sc-protestor-fund">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Charleston, SC Protestor Fund is a general community fund to help any Black Lives Matter protestors in the Charleston, SC area receive bail funds should they need it. We are in the early stages so please stayed tuned for more info. This is not officially affiliated with any organization or organizer, this is created by allies wanting to help create positive change.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/chicago-community-bond-fund</guid><title>The Chicago Community Bond Fund (CCBF)</title><description>The Chicago Community Bond Fund (CCBF) pays bond for people charged with crimes in Cook County, Illinois.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/chicago-community-bond-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://chicagobond.org/">The Chicago Community Bond Fund (CCBF)</a></h1><h2><a href="https://chicagobond.org/donate/">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Chicago Community Bond Fund (CCBF) pays bond for people charged with crimes in Cook County, Illinois. Through a revolving fund, CCBF supports individuals whose communities cannot afford to pay the bonds themselves and who have been impacted by structural violence. Inability to pay bond results in higher rates of conviction, longer sentences, loss of housing and jobs, separation of families, and lost custody of children. By paying bond, CCBF restores the presumption of innocence before trial and enables recipients to remain free while fighting their cases. CCBF also engages in public education about the role of bond in the criminal legal system and advocates for the abolition of money bond. CCBF is committed to long-term relationship building and organizing with people most directly impacted by criminalization and policing.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/cuapb-mn</guid><title>Communities United Against Police Brutality</title><description>Communities United Against Police Brutality is a Twin-Cities based organization that was created to deal with police brutality on an ongoing basis</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/cuapb-mn</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.cuapb.org/">Communities United Against Police Brutality</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.paypal.com/donate/?token=4XcNfQFUdyzy68NrQiMs-AoyZE7cOEw1f-K-5llu_I5NqMPkvTdk4g06M2vMisR7vTlNQ0&country.x=US&locale.x=US">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Communities United Against Police Brutality is a Twin-Cities based organization that was created to deal with police brutality on an ongoing basis. We work on the day-to-day abuses as well as taking on the more extreme cases. Our overriding goal is to create a climate of resistance to abuse of authority by police organizations and to empower local people with a structure that can take on police brutality and actually bring it to an end. We provide support for survivors of police brutality and families of victims so they can reclaim their dignity and join the struggle to end police brutality.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/detroit-justice</guid><title>The Detroit Justice Center (DJC)</title><description>The Detroit Justice Center (DJC) is a non-profit law firm working alongside communities to create economic opportunities, transform the justice system, and promote equitable and just cities.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/detroit-justice</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="">The Detroit Justice Center (DJC)</a></h1><h2><a href="https://donorbox.org/support-the-detroit-justice-center-1">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Detroit Justice Center (DJC) is a non-profit law firm working alongside communities to create economic opportunities, transform the justice system, and promote equitable and just cities.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/go-get-it-tobacco</guid><title>Go Get It Tobacco</title><description>We are a Black-Owned Business supporting local community members, designers, and entrepreneurs across our great state. It’s rare to see a Tobacco owner who is Black, which was why we opened the store. We stand with the movement for Black Lives.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/go-get-it-tobacco</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/z8puys-gogetit?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Go Get It Tobacco</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/z8puys-gogetit?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Donate Here</a></h2><p>We appreciate all of your concern and support. Unfortunately, Go Get It Tobacco was broken into and robbed last night in the midst of the pain and trauma since the death of George Floyd. We are absolutely devastated - both of the death of George Floyd and of the challenge it will be to rebuild.</p><p>But we know buildings do not matter more than Black Lives.</p><p>We are a Black-Owned Business supporting local community members, designers, and entrepreneurs across our great state.</p><p>It’s rare to see a Tobacco owner who is Black, which was why we opened the store. We stand with the movement for Black Lives.</p><p>We support the community during this challenging time.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/guns-and-roses-boutique</guid><title>Guns and Roses Boutique</title><description>Guns and Roses Boutique has been a staple in Dallas, TX  for over 8 years.  On Friday, May 29, 2020 the boutique was destroyed by selfish looters who took advantage of the protest. The restoration of Guns and Roses Boutique starts NOW!</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/guns-and-roses-boutique</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/fv47qs-protect-our-community?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Guns and Roses Boutique</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/fv47qs-protect-our-community?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Guns and Roses Boutique has been a staple in Dallas, TX for over 8 years. On Friday, May 29, 2020 the boutique was destroyed by selfish looters who took advantage of the protest. The restoration of Guns and Roses Boutique starts NOW!</p><p>Princess Pope, Owner and Leader has been a prominent pillar in the community, known to give the shirt off her back, she has put blood, sweat and tears into her business. As a fashion industry leader, she provides education and mentorship to aspiring Fashion Designers and Entrepreneurs. Let's get Guns and Roses back open again. All donations will go towards any expenses needed to reopen the boutique that insurance does not cover! We appreciate your support!</p><p>THIS IS THE OFFICIAL GO FUND ACCOUNT! Any other support pages are not associated with Guns And Roses Boutique.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/massachusetts-bail-fund</guid><title>Massachusetts Bail Fund</title><description>The Massachusetts Bail Fund pays up to $2000 bail so that low-income people can stay free while they work towards resolving their case, allowing individuals, families, and communities to stay productive, together, and stable.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/massachusetts-bail-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.massbailfund.org/">Massachusetts Bail Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.massbailfund.org/donate.html">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Massachusetts Bail Fund pays up to $2000 bail so that low-income people can stay free while they work towards resolving their case, allowing individuals, families, and communities to stay productive, together, and stable. The Massachusetts Bail Fund is committed to the harm reduction of freeing individuals serving pre-trial sentences, and to abolishing pre-trial detention and supervision in the long-term.<br>​ Massachusetts jails are filled with people awaiting trial simply because they cannot afford bail. Bail leads to longer incarcerations times, lost jobs, lost housing, and devastated families. The Massachusetts Bail Fund provides up to $200 bail for low-income individuals.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/milwaukee-freedom-fund</guid><title>Milwaukee Freedom Fund</title><description>The Milwaukee Freedom Fund was started by Black and Brown Milwaukee organizers who want to see residents supported as they assert their right to protest for justice.  We are raising money and gathering resources for bail, court-related costs, rides, food, water, and other needs, as the community struggles for liberation.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/milwaukee-freedom-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://fundrazr.com/mkefreedomfund?ref=fb_19CDk2_ab_9LbNijpg6rg9LbNijpg6rg(">Milwaukee Freedom Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://fundrazr.com/mkefreedomfund?ref=fb_19CDk2_ab_9LbNijpg6rg9LbNijpg6rg">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Milwaukee Freedom Fund was started by Black and Brown Milwaukee organizers who want to see residents supported as they assert their right to protest for justice. We are raising money and gathering resources for bail, court-related costs, rides, food, water, and other needs, as the community struggles for liberation.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/minnesota-freedom-fund</guid><title>Minnesota Freedom Fund</title><description>The Minnesota Freedom Fund pays criminal bail and immigration bond for those who cannot afford to as we seek to end discriminatory, coercive, and oppressive jailing.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/minnesota-freedom-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://minnesotafreedomfund.org/">Minnesota Freedom Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://minnesotafreedomfund.org/donate">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Minnesota Freedom Fund pays criminal bail and immigration bond for those who cannot afford to as we seek to end discriminatory, coercive, and oppressive jailing.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/mississsippi-bail-fund-collective</guid><title>The Mississippi Bail Fund Collective</title><description>The Mississippi Bail Fund Collective was created to put an end to the injustice caused by the bail system. We bail poor people out of jail.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/mississsippi-bail-fund-collective</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://secure.actblue.com/donate/ms-bail-fund">The Mississippi Bail Fund Collective</a></h1><h2><a href="https://secure.actblue.com/donate/ms-bail-fund">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Mississippi Bail Fund Collective was created to put an end to the injustice caused by the bail system. We bail poor people out of jail! And we offer compassionate help to reverse the inevitable damage that they and their families face after an unjust imprisonment. Your donation will ensure everyday Mississippians have the same chance to receive justice as those that have money. Every dollar makes a difference!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/montgomery-bailout-fund</guid><title>Montgomery Bail Out</title><description>We are raising money to provide support and post bail for people in the Montgomery County Jail. Our friends, loved ones, and comrades in Montgomery's crowded, unsanitary jails are especially endangered by the ongoing spread of COVID-19. When our government leaders fail to take appropriate action to keep us safe, the community must step up. That is why we are inviting you to join us in launching the Montgomery Bail Out.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/montgomery-bailout-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.mgmbailout.com/">Montgomery Bail Out</a></h1><h2><a href="https://givebutter.com/mgmbailout">Donate Here</a></h2><p>We are raising money to provide support and post bail for people in the Montgomery County Jail. Our friends, loved ones, and comrades in Montgomery's crowded, unsanitary jails are especially endangered by the ongoing spread of COVID-19. When our government leaders fail to take appropriate action to keep us safe, the community must step up. That is why we are inviting you to join us in launching the Montgomery Bail Out.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/nashville-bail-fund</guid><title>The Nashville Community Bail Fund</title><description>The Nashville Community Bail Fund frees low-income persons from jail, connects with their loved ones, and works to end wealth-based detention through community partnerships</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/nashville-bail-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://nashvillebailfund.org/">The Nashville Community Bail Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://nashvillebailfund.org/">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Nashville Community Bail Fund frees low-income persons from jail, connects with their loved ones, and works to end wealth-based detention through community partnerships</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/new-orleans-safety-and-freedom-fund</guid><title>New Orleans Safety and Freedom Fund</title><description>Together, we will make New Orleans a safer, more equitable place to live, by redesigning the role money plays in the criminal justice system. Safety and Freedom Fund supporters make both social and economic impact.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/new-orleans-safety-and-freedom-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.facebook.com/SafetyAndFreedomFund/">New Orleans Safety and Freedom Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://donorbox.org/safety-freedom-fund-eoy">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Together, we will make New Orleans a safer, more equitable place to live, by redesigning the role money plays in the criminal justice system.</p><p>Safety and Freedom Fund supporters make both social and economic impact.</p><p>In addition to helping a fellow New Orleanian maintain their dignity and liberty as they fight their case, research shows that posting bail on someone's behalf recovers an average of $2,000 in economic opportunity otherwise lost while sitting in jail unable to work.</p><p>And by deepening your understanding about the role that money (bail, drug testing fees, jail release fees, fines, etc.) plays in the system, Safety and Freedom Fund supporters contribute to long-term systemic change. Over the coming years, we will partner with impact litigators, legislators and grassroots organizations to rewrite the laws that govern the flow of money in this system.</p><p>The New Orleans Safety and Freedom Fund is a program of Operation Restoration, a 501c3 non-profit organization.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/no-new-jails-nyc</guid><title>No New Jails NYC</title><description>No New Jails NYC is a direct continuation of the grassroots efforts to close Rikers immediately, No New Jails NYC also draws on the success of previous of jail construction fights in NYC.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/no-new-jails-nyc</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.nonewjails.nyc/">No New Jails NYC</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.paypal.com/pools/c/8exBHLvYm8">Donate Here</a></h2><p>No New Jails NYC formed in September 2018, shortly after the Mayor launched the formal land-use approval process for the jail expansion plan. A direct continuation of the grassroots efforts to close Rikers immediately, No New Jails NYC also draws on the success of previous of jail construction fights in NYC.</p><p>From May to November 2019, the Mayor’s jail expansion plan will be put before a string of public bodies and officials, each with increasing power, to say yea or nay to rezoning neighborhood locations in Manhattan, Queens, Brooklyn, and the Bronx for the Mayor’s massive new jails via the Uniform Land Use Review Procedure (ULURP) process.</p><p>At the same time, No New Jails NYC is building power in communities throughout New York City and with its incarcerated members. Overwhelmingly, New Yorkers agree that all efforts should be dedicated now to closing all jails on Rikers Island, that there is no need to build any more jails, and that the billions of dollars budgeted for new jails should be redirected instead to community-based resources that will support permanent decarceration.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/oakland-indie-alliance</guid><title>Oakland Indie Alliance (OIA)</title><description>We exist to keep Oakland local and independent. We are a community of local, independent business owners in Oakland.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/oakland-indie-alliance</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="http://www.oaklandindiealliance.com/">Oakland Indie Alliance (OIA)</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.paypal.com/donate/?token=sNl3CP23cyNa0MYC3G0vrZnOf_c2CjVgFsBS4cd2e9YMnJYlwwIy7cmJQ_iIvlLybDIZK0&country.x=US&locale.x=US">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Founded in 2014, the Oakland Indie Alliance (OIA) is a community of more than 300 small-scale entrepreneurs who have united under a common goal of preserving Oakland’s variety, energy, and social fabric. Through sharing experiences, connections, and advocating for Oakland’s independent economy, OIA allows small businesses to thrive.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/oakland-lgbtq-community-center</guid><title>Oakland LGBTQ+ Community Center</title><description>The Oakland LGBTQ Community Center's model of service delivery is "wellness first" and provides social, educational, and holistic health-related programs, services and activities.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/oakland-lgbtq-community-center</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.oaklandlgbtqcenter.org/">Oakland LGBTQ+ Community Center</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.oaklandlgbtqcenter.org/support-us">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Oakland finally has its very own LGBTQ Community Center! Established in 2017, the Oakland LGBTQ+ Community Center is a Non-Profit, 501(c)(3), tax exempt organization, located in the beautiful Lake Merritt district. We welcome you to come in, check out our service offerings on our calendar, and get involved—this is YOUR Center! The Oakland LGBTQ Community Center's model of service delivery is "wellness first" and provides social, educational, and holistic health-related programs, services and activities.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/official-george-floyd-memorial-fund</guid><title>Official George Floyd Memorial Fund</title><description></description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/official-george-floyd-memorial-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/georgefloyd">Official George Floyd Memorial Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/georgefloyd">Donate Here</a></h2><p>On May 25, 2020, my life shattered as I learned of the tragic passing of my dear brother, George.</p><p>My family and I watched in absolute horror as the now infamous and horrifying video began to spread quickly throughout social media. What we saw on that tape left us shell shocked; a white Minneapolis police officer kneeling directly on my brother's neck, obstructing his ability to breathe. As some officers knelt on his neck, other officers participated and watched; no one took any action to save my brother's life. Those officers would continue to brutalize my brother until he died. This fund is established to cover funeral and burial expenses, mental and grief counseling, lodging and travel for all court proceedings, and to assist our family in the days to come as we continue to seek justice for George. A portion of these funds will also go to the Estate of George Floyd for the benefit and care of his children and their educational fund.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/peoples-city-council-la</guid><title>People’s City Council LA</title><description>People’s City Council (PCC) is an actions-oriented coalition of social and climate justice organizations and organizers from all over Los Angeles. PCC emerged in the absence of definitive City action to protect the most vulnerable — the unhoused and tenants.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/peoples-city-council-la</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.peoplescitycouncil-la.com/">People’s City Council LA</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/peoples-city-council-ticket-fund">Donate Here</a>_</h2><p>People’s City Council (PCC) is an actions-oriented coalition of social and climate justice organizations and organizers from all over Los Angeles. PCC emerged in the absence of definitive City action to protect the most vulnerable — the unhoused and tenants. The LA City Council repeatedly failed to enact protective measures, putting our neighbors at increasing risk during a time when they are worried about the health of their families and communities. We formed to call attention to the failures of Mayor Eric Garcetti and the Los Angeles City Council. At the same time, we have a mission to uplift the work being done every day, on the ground, by neighbors helping neighbors, organizing, and building community power — a Peoples’ City Council made up of communities fighting for an LA that is racially, economically, and environmentally just. We continue to evolve to meet the needs of our comrades. This dynamism is what makes us who we are.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/philadelphia-community-bail-fund</guid><title>The Philadelphia Community Bail Fund</title><description>The Philadelphia Community Bail Fund raises money all year round to post bail for our neighbors who remain imprisoned simply because they are too poor to pay for their freedom.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/philadelphia-community-bail-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.phillybailout.com/">The Philadelphia Community Bail Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.aplos.com/aws/give/PhiladelphiaCommunityBailfund/general">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The Philadelphia Community Bail Fund raises money all year round to post bail for our neighbors who remain imprisoned simply because they are too poor to pay for their freedom. Your support goes toward posting bail and providing some basic supports to help people recover their lives after incarceration. These supports include transit passes so that people can get to court or work. Help paying back rent or securing an apartment when incarceration has threatened their housing. Money for groceries and clothing.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/reclaim-the-block-minneapolis</guid><title>Reclaim the Block</title><description>Reclaim the Block began in 2018 and organizes Minneapolis community and city council members to move money from the police department into other areas of the city’s budget that truly promote community health and safety.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/reclaim-the-block-minneapolis</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.reclaimtheblock.org/">Reclaim the Block</a></h1><h2><a href="https://secure.everyaction.com/zae4prEeKESHBy0MKXTIcQ2">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Reclaim the Block began in 2018 and organizes Minneapolis community and city council members to move money from the police department into other areas of the city’s budget that truly promote community health and safety. We believe health, safety and resiliency exist without police of any kind. We organize around policies that strengthen community-led safety initiatives and reduce reliance on police departments. We do not believe that increased regulation of or public engagement with the police will lead to safer communities, as community testimony and documented police conduct suggest otherwise.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/richmond-community-bail-fund</guid><title>Richmond Community Bail Fund</title><description>A community bail fund that provides cash bail to defendants who cannot afford to pay it. As a revolving bail fund, donations will benefit multiple clients over time as funds are returned following the disposition of trials.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/richmond-community-bail-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://rvabailfund.org/">Richmond Community Bail Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://rvabailfund.org/donate">Donate Here</a></h2><p>A community bail fund that provides cash bail to defendants who cannot afford to pay it. As a revolving bail fund, donations will benefit multiple clients over time as funds are returned following the disposition of trials.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/sac-delux-onsignment-store</guid><title>SacDelux Consignment Store</title><description>SacDelux is a luxury consignment business, built, owned and operated by Shanice Gaither and Nikki Hightower.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/sac-delux-onsignment-store</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-sacdelux-consignment-store?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">SacDelux Consignment Store</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-sacdelux-consignment-store?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Donate Here</a></h2><p>SacDelux is a luxury consignment business, built, owned and operated by Shanice Gaither and Nikki Hightower.</p><p>Since 2014, these ladies have worked to establish their business &amp; brand not only for means to support theirselves, but also the profitability of individuals.</p><p>As a consignment store, a large majority of their inventory consists of gently used luxury items provided by clients looking for a return on their luxury investments.<br><br>Although insurance and theft protection measures were take to secure their clients belongings, the fight to reclaim the losses they have experienced will be ongoing and not guaranteed.</p><p>While the cost of their inventory and damages are astronomical every dollar will count toward reopening this small business and ensuring that all clients receive compensation for trusting SacDelux as their preferred luxury consignment store.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/scores-sports-bar-mpls</guid><title>Scores Sports Bar Mpls</title><description>Scores Sports Bar was LOOTED,  VANDALIZED and DESTROYED 5/27/2020. This black-owned business is left trying to pick up the pieces amidst mourning with the community.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/scores-sports-bar-mpls</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/scores-bar-mpls-riot-rebuild?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Scores Sports Bar Mpls</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/scores-bar-mpls-riot-rebuild?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=p_cp+share-sheet">Donate Here</a></h2><p>Scores Sports Bar was set for a grand opening this spring but when COVID-19 hit that was put on pause. Now, just as Scores was gearing up to welcome customers with updated guidelines from the govenor, George Floyd was murdered and everything changed overnight.</p><p>Scores Sports Bar was LOOTED, VANDALIZED and DESTROYED 5/27/2020. This black-owned business is left trying to pick up the pieces amidst mourning with the community.</p><p>About the Bar Owners: Kb Balla &amp; his wife Twyana are active members of their community. KB is a Firefighter on the Brooklyn Center Fire Department and Twyana was a member of the Sounds of Blackness. They have a 4 beautiful children and the toll of this entire situation is heavy. KB has been a community entrepreneur for decades and coaches and contributes to the community in which they live.</p><p>Anything you can donate to start the rebuild process will be a blessing</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/small-black-owned-business-long-beach</guid><title>Small LB BlackOwned Business Looted &amp; Set on Fire</title><description></description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/small-black-owned-business-long-beach</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/small-lb-blackowned-business-looted-amp-set-on-fire">Small LB BlackOwned Business Looted &amp; Set on Fire</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/small-lb-blackowned-business-looted-amp-set-on-fire">Donate Here</a></h2><p>On the night of May 31st, 2020 during the looting and rioting occurring in Downtown Long Beach, my dad's barbershop/hair salon was affected by the actions of those who chose to set small businesses along Pine Street on fire. My dad, Chris "Fontayne" Herron, has put 10 years of sweat, blood, and tears into his shop and it so disappointing to know that his black-owned business was burned to the ground in spite of all that is happening in today's society. He has done nothing but give back to his community, for example running an annual toy run in Long Beach, CA (Popeye's Toy Run) every December for the past 12 years in remembrance of my grandpa, in which we give back to the people of our community by collecting donations of toys, bikes, gift cards, electronics, etc. He is also very active on Skid Row, working with Beauty 2 The Streetz where he volunteers and offers free haircuts to those in need on Skid Row. He watched his shop burn down right in front of him and could do nothing to make the fire stop fast enough. My dad is still in a state of shock and devastation and I know the help from people within our community and out would mean the world to him! It would mean so much to my dad and our family if those reading this could donate or simply just share this post so that he can try to rebuild all that was lost. Anything helps!!!</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://blm-donate.com/posts/tampa-bay-community-support-fund</guid><title>Tampa Bay Community Support Fund</title><description>The donations being used will provide community support for those who have had their civil liberties infringed upon by local law enforcement on 5/30 and 5/31 during peaceful Justice for George Floyd Event.</description><link>https://blm-donate.com/posts/tampa-bay-community-support-fund</link><pubDate>Thu, 4 Jun 2020 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/tampa-bay-community-support-fund">Tampa Bay Community Support Fund</a></h1><h2><a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/tampa-bay-community-support-fund">Donate Here</a></h2><p>The donations being used will provide community support for those who have had their civil liberties infringed upon by local law enforcement on 5/30 and 5/31 during peaceful Justice for George Floyd Event. We are providing relief for both medical expenses and community support for those affected by their civil liberties being deprived. We will use this fund to to offer medical reimbursement and bond reimbursement for individuals whose rights were infringed upon as a result of the protest.</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>